http://www.angloamerican.co.uk/site-services/privacy-policy

.
SHARE
This Privacy Notice (or "Notice") is provided by Anglo American plc and our group companies (the "Company", "we", "our" or "us") and is intended to provide you with all of the information that you need to understand the personal data that we may have about you.
In particular, the Notice describes the categories of personal data we may process, how your personal data may be processed and how your privacy is safeguarded in the course of our relationship with you.
It is intended to comply with our obligations to provide you with information about the Company's processing of your personal data.
We take your data protection rights and our legal obligations seriously. Your personal data will be treated in a secure and confidential manner and only as detailed in this Notice.
The Notice is divided into sections, which relate to the type of relationship that you have with the Company.
Each section will give you information relating to the way we manage personal data in each of the types of relationship or interaction that we may have with you.
Please ensure that you review the Overview pages carefully, as these will apply to you regardless of our relationship with you.
Of course, not all of the sections in the Notice will be relevant to everyone.
The Notice is intended to provide details of all the processing activities that we undertake and therefore the mere listing of an activity in this Notice does not mean that we are processing your personal data in this manner and for these purposes.
If you have any questions about how the information presented relates to you, please do contact us using the relevant contact details appearing in the contact us section.
Overview
Read more
Overview
Each of the five sections below will give you information relating to the way we manage personal data in each of the types of relationship or interaction that we may have with you:
Website users
Read more
Website users
Customers and prospects
Read more
Customers and prospects
Stakeholders
Read more
Further information:
